cyberport.hk 2019-08-07

# Hong Kong Cyberport Management Company Limited - Privacy Policy Statement

In this Policy, “we” refers to Hong Kong Cyberport Management Company Limited 香港數碼港管理有限公司and "Ordinance" refers to the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance, Chapter 486 of the laws of Hong Kong.

###    
**Your Privacy**

We are committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of our customers, visitors and website users ("Users" or "you") by observing and ensuring full compliance with the requirements stipulated under the Ordinance.  We recognize that when you choose to provide us with information about yourself, you trust us to act in a responsible manner.  That's why we have put a policy in place to protect your personal data.  Please read on for more details on how we handle your personal data.

###    
**What data does Cyberport collect and how do we use it?**

When you visit our website we will record your visit only as a “hit”.  The web-server makes a record of your visit that includes your IP addresses (and domain names), the types and configurations of browsers, language settings, geo-locations, operating systems, previous sites visited (visitor data ** _)_**.  We use such visitor data only for website enhancement, optimization and “security incident investigation” (e.g. tracing the origin of a suspected hacker’s attack).

At times, we may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal data. The personal data may be obtained by electronic means or in written form.  Generally, this data is requested when you register for an event organized by Cyberport, when you attend to events organized by Cyberport, subscribe to a service provided by Cyberport or when you subscribe for Cyberport’s electronic news.  When you enter a promotional event such as training, symposium etc., we may ask for your name, company name, contact number and e-mail address so we can administer the event and notify you of the registration status.  Personal data held by us will be used for the purposes specified from time to time.  Please refer to our [Personal Information Collection Statement](http://www.cyberport.hk/en/pics) on how we may use your personal data and to whom we may transfer or disclose your personal data, and your right of access to and correction of your personal data held by us.

###    
**Will Cyberport disclose or transfer the data it collects to outside parties?**

Cyberport will NOT disclose or transfer personal data collected to outside parties unless such disclosure or transfer is authorised, required or permitted by, or in compliance with, the Ordinance.  Please refer to our [Personal Data Collection Statement](http://www.cyberport.hk/en/pics) for details.

###    
**Data Security**

We are required by the Ordinance to take all reasonable practicable steps to safeguard the security of personal data held by us. Cyberport will strive to protect any personal data held by us against unauthorized access or processing.  Our web-servers are hardened, protected behind "firewalls" in order to prevent unauthorized virtual access. Measures have been implemented to protect the web-servers against physical harm or theft.

Notwithstanding our obligation to safeguard the security of personal data, we are unable to guarantee complete security of communications through the internet given the open nature of the internet. You will have to assess and accept the relevant risks before sending personal data to us via our web site.

###    
**Use of Cookies**

When you browse this website, cookies will be stored in your computer's hard drive.  Most web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can choose to “not accept” cookies by changing the setting but if you do so you may find that font resizing function may not work properly or may not be available.  The data collected by means of cookies on the website about you include the current version of your operating system and web browser and will be used only for compiling aggregate statistics on how visitors browse the website for the purpose of managing and improving the design of the website.

###    
**Accuracy and Retention of Personal Data**

We are required by the Ordinance to take all reasonable practicable steps to ensure that personal data held by us (i) is accurate having regard to the purposes for which the data is to be used; and (ii) is not kept longer than is necessary for the fulfillment of the purpose for which the data is to be used unless otherwise permitted by the Ordinance or required by any applicable legal or regulatory requirements.  Please note that personal data collected from a User who has registered on our website to receive direct marketing materials will be retained for that purpose until he cancels his registration.

###    
**Direct Marketing**

Subject to the applicable requirements under the Ordinance, we may from time to time send direct marketing materials promoting services, products, facilities or activities to you using your personal data. Please refer to our [Personal Information Collection Statement](http://www.cyberport.hk/en/pics) for details. Opt-out channel or facilities will be provided to enable you to exercise your right to opt out from direct marketing.

We will not provide your personal data to third parties for direct marketing or other unrelated purposes without your consent.

Despite your provision of consent to use your personal data for direct marketing, you may at any time notify your intention to withdraw such consent.

###    
**Links to other Web Sites**

Our website may contain links to other web sites maintained by other persons, which may collect your personal data in the course of your interaction with these persons.  The collection and use of personal data by these persons are beyond our control and are subject to the privacy policies of the relevant persons.

###    
**Access to Personal Data and Correction Requests**

You have a right under the Ordinance to request access to and/or correction of your Personal Data held by us.  Please refer to our [Personal Information Collection Statement](http://www.cyberport.hk/en/pics) on how to make data access requests or data correction requests.

###    
**Tell us what you think**

Our goal is to respect your privacy.  To help us improve our privacy policies, please give us your feedback.  We welcome your comments and questions.
